Masshiro na keshiki ni ima sasowarete
Boku wa yuku yo mada minu sekai e
Woah
Maigo no mama tabi shiteita
nezumiiro no sora no shita
Higawari no chizu
ikutsumo no yume ga nijinde ita
Itsuka wa sa chippoke na
boku no kono hohaba demo
Ano kumo no mukou made yukeru kana
Tsuyogatte kizutsuita kokoro sukashita you ni
Furidashita amatsubutachi ga
ranhansha kurikaesu
Massugu na hikari ga kousa shite
Yukusaki mo tsugenu mama
dokomademo tsukinukeru
Awai zanzou ryoume ni yakistukete
Kono sora no shita donna toko ni ite mo
Todoku hazu nanda mada minu sekai e
A smoke bomb and a grenade in one.
That reckless fool is
beginning to annoy me.
Do you think you can follow their scent?
Uh-huh!
Here, officer.
Take her somewhere she'll be safe.
Winry, Al is still
fighting, so I have to go.
Okay?
Okay? I'm sorry.
When this is over, I'll explain everything.
Why?
Why is waiting the only thing I can do?
We have a girl in custody
in Sector 8 who appears
to be a friend of the
Fullmetal Alchemist.
Escort her to Central Command.
Repeat, Sector 8.
We have a girl in custody who appears
to be a friend of the Fullmetal Alchemist...
It's just about time.
...Escort her to Central Command.
Go and back them up.
Right.
There's a vacant house outside of town.
That's where we'll meet up.
Don't be followed.
Okay.
If something goes wrong, I'll let you know.
All right.
And Sir, please stay out of the field.
I know, Lieutenant. Now go.
You won't give up.
This area looks deserted.
A dead end. We're trapped.
Hmm?
Scar again.
Gluttony, go see what he's up to this time.
And I'll take care of our
two little friends here.
What happened to me?
What's wrong?
My arm. My lord.
I'm useless to you now.
What are you talking about?
You cannot burden yourself with me.
If you do, they'll only get you too.
A king is no king without his people,
But a people without their
king would be lost as well.
You can't do that to them.
My lord, think of our clan!
You must live for their sake.
I won't leave you!
Sometimes someone must be left behind.
For the greater good.
Lan Fan? What are you planning?!
No! Don't do it!
Watch out!
There's nothing inside that armor.
You're hollow, aren't you?
You poor boy.
Alchemy trapped you in that metal prison
and yet you still have faith in it.
True, there are plenty of things
about this body that are inconvenient.
But it's nothing I can't live with.
I don't need pity from anyone.
Least of all from you.
My brother used alchemy to save my life.
To regret the form I have now would
mean not only rejecting alchemy,
but also turning my back on him.
I believe in my brother
and I believe in alchemy.
I will not lose faith.
I want to believe!
Oh, do you?
Brother, where's Winry?
She's safe.
No thanks to me, though.
I made her cry again.
You really should be more careful, brother.
She doesn't like to
see you fight like that.
Yeah.
But she's gone now.
Let's end this!
Oh, I found you!
The Ishvalan!
You again.
Look at his tattoo!
Homunculus.
Huh?
It's Ling!
Go! Move it!
[GASP]
Get me some strong cable.
Right! On it!
Your own regenerative ability
is working against you.
Your flesh won't stop expanding .
It'll keep you tied up nice and tight.
You're mine now,
Homunculus!
That was well played, girl.
I beat you.
How does it feel to be tricked?
You lose this round.
What?
That thing is a Homunculus?
Put him in. We're getting out of here.
Huh?
Ah!
Hold on a sec, Lieutenant.
Shh!
- Wait! What's going on?
- Al!
The MPs are watching.
Just pretend we don't know her.
They're getting away! After them!
Right!
The Colonel may be a creep and a jerk,
but at least we can trust him.
We have something to do.
We have to get him, Al!
You killed the Rockbells
and Nina, among many others!
You're going to answer for your crimes!
Are these two giving you trouble, servant?
This is the servant of the
man who saved my life.
You better leave him alone,
puny little boy!
Wait a sec! Who are you calling puny?!
Where'd that kid come from?
Get away, girl. It's dangerous.
They've got us outnumbered.
It's time for us to retreat!
Ha!
Ah!
[COUGHING]
What kind of alchemy was that?
She did it from that far away?
Here, follow me.
I can't see.
Scar!
[CAR HORN, TIRES SCREECHING]
I know who you are, Ling Yao.
Don't worry.
We're on our way to a secure safe house.
My friend! I left her behind.
Go get her!
What?!
No, we can't. We don't have time.
Make time! She could be dying now.
She's still waiting there for me!
You had better make it quick.
[CAR HORN]
Huh?
That woman driving...
I'm sure she's Mustang's.
I'm tired of playing
games with that upstart.
Fullmetal Alchemist.
Her eyes... Is that
how mine looked?
No matter what I do,
hatred only breeds more hatred.
There you go.
I think I managed to stop the bleeding.
Thank you.
Sir, the MPs are all closing in on us.
We need to get going.
He took a shot to the leg.
In his condition,
he couldn't have gotten far.
- Comb the area for him!
-[DOGS BARKING]
Sir!
Quickly, sir! Quickly!
Xiao-Mei, where are you?
Oh, no.
Look what I found, Ed!
We're a little busy right now
to be adopting panda bears, Al!
I couldn't leave her alone in the
middle of all that mess back there!
First stray cats and now this!
Just how many animals can you
stuff into that armor of yours, huh?!
Get rid of it!
What a heartless thing to say!
Look how sweet and gentle she is.
[TINY GROWL]
[GIGGLES]
It's all right, you're safe now.
This way. Follow me.
Thanks.
You can stay in here, okay?
Hey, Winry!
Oh!
Hello there, Fullmetal Alchemist.
Fuhrer Bradley, this is a surprise.
What brings you here?
I heard that a childhood
friend of yours was
under our protection here
at the Command Center.
As a friend of such an important alchemist,
she deserves our every courtesy.
I should be on my way now.
If you'll please excuse me, miss.
Oh, of course, sir.
That's a nice, honest
friend you've got there.
Make sure you both take good care of her.
Ed?
Huh?
You promised.
Tell me everything about my parents.
What happened to them?
I see.
They did everything they could to
help others, right up until the end.
But I...
I just wish they could have
come back to me alive.
Is that selfish?
More waiting.
That's all I can ever do.
Ah, perfect timing.
Miss Rockbell, there's
a telephone call for you.
For me?
Yes, hello?
Oh, Mr. Garfiel!
I'm sorry about this, Winry...
I know you've got a lot going on,
and I tried to handle it myself, really.
- Where is she?
- Isn't Winry back yet?
Look at this!
Winry's the only one who can fix it.
But I can't take this anymore,
your customers are so needy!
Please hurry back, Winry! We miss you!
You there, Miss Winry?
Tetsu?
Please come back to the shop soon.
You do a much better job working
on my leg than Mr. Garfiel can!
We need you here!
Yeah, another thing, Winry,
We still need an outer covering
for that model leg you made for me.
- My arm needs work, too!
- Hey, hold on a sec! I was first!
Miss you, Winry!
You idiot, of course you miss her!
We all do.
Isn't that the truth!
I'm sorry.
I'll be back home soon.
Just hold on.
I won't be much longer.
I'll help everyone.
Thank you all.
Thank you both...
for stopping me back there.
I forgot there were still
people who depended on me.
If I had done it, I wouldn't have
been able to face them again.
Of course.
I expect you to take good
care of your auto mail.
Yep.
Oh, and I'll send you some
good polishing oil soon, Al.
Great!
And no dying, okay?
Right.
Oh, and...
The next time I make you cry,
I hope that they'll be...[TRAIN WHISTLE]
Huh? What?
I can't hear you!
Brother? Wait up!
See ya, Winry!
Okay...jeez.
Come back, Edward!
What were you saying?
The next time I make you cry,
I hope they'll be tears of joy!
Then Al and I will be
back in our normal bodies,
and I'll make you cry
out of sheer happiness!
That's a promise!
[LAUGHS]
Give me a new arm and a leg.
I need one year.
Well...
There's no turning
back for us now, brother.
What are you crying for, Winry?
All this time...have I been...
Falling for him?
Colonel!
Get in the car.
Someone's badly injured.
I came to you because we need a doctor.
Got yourself in trouble again.
Just can't help yourself.
I know you have a family.
I wouldn't want to endanger them.
If you'd rather not get
involved, I'll understand.
Wait here. I'll get my instruments.
You sure about this?
My wife and I split up not long
after I came back from duty in Ishval.
You let her wander around
the sewers with her arm cut off?
Don't blame me if she gets lockjaw.
I'm afraid the only patients
I've had lately have been corpses,
so this might be a little rough.
[LAN FAN SCREAMING]
- I'm sorry—
- No, don't apologize.
I'm the one who suggested it, remember?
We both had something to
gain out of it, so it made sense.
When I went in search of immortality,
I knew I must be ready
to make certain sacrifices.
But I...
I wasn't ready for this.
Lan Fan was, though.
She made the decision
that I was too weak to make.
[WHIMPERING]
[GASPS]
She's awake!
You okay? Is there anything we can do?
That old trap of yours worked pretty well.
But I'm useless without my arm.
I'm going to need to find a replacement.
You know, I can introduce
you to a great engineer.
I'm with the state military.
Name's Colonel Roy Mustang.
And my name is Ling Yao,
the twelfth son of the Emperor of Xing.
I appreciate you finding a doctor.
It was no problem.
Thank you for helping
us with the Ross incident.
And also...
for bringing this thing in.
Hey, what do we have here?
That's Gluttony. He's a Homunculus.
He and his friends
appear to have connections
among some of the
military's senior staff.
[GASP]
Just some, you say?
It goes far deeper than that.
Your Führer King Bradley?
I believe it's possible that
he's a Homunculus too.
[GASPS]
I saw his eye.
The one under the patch,
it had an Ouroboros tattoo.
He and Gluttony came after us
and they were working together.
No way!
Our ruler? A Homunculus?
Although...
Bradley doesn't have the same sort of
inhuman presence that you get from Gluttony.
At his core, he still feels
like a regular person.
Another thing, if the Führer is a
Homunculus, how can he possibly have a son?
It's said in that book that the Homunculi
have no reproductive capabilities.
No, the Führer's son Selim is adopted.
There's no direct blood relation
between him and his father.
[ROY SCOFFS]
AL: Huh?
Whether he's monster or human,
either way, these new developments will make
it easier to remove him from the seat of power.
First, we get information out of this one.
And I'll take his stone.
It may prove useful in treating my man.
Hey, you!
Lan Fan lost her arm to get him!
He's our captive!
We're taking him back to Xing!
Hold it!
He could help us get our bodies back!
We've been working on that for a long time.
I'm not gonna let you
just waltz off with him!
That's right!
Think about it, Ling.
You're an illegal alien!
I'm too old for this kind of thing.
Good luck, Mustang. I'm going home.
Listen to me...
Colonel Mustang.
Mustang was one who killed Lust.
Mustang must pay for what he did to her!
Roy Mustang!
What was that?!
Let it all out, let it all out
Tsuyogaranakute ii n da ne
Dareka ga kaite'tta
Kabe no rakugaki no hana ga yureru
Jibunrashisa nante, dare mo wakaranai yo
Nagai nagai michi no tochuu
de nakushitari, hirottari,
Kyuu ni samishiku natte,
naichau hi mo aru kedo
Namida mo itami mo, hoshi ni kaeyou
Ashita wo terasu akari wo tomosou
Chiisana te kazashite
futari de tsukurou hoshikuzu wo
Tsuyoku hikaru ein wo
Sayonara itsuka wa kuru ka mo shirenu
Kisetsu wa sore demo meguri megutte'ku
Chiisaku mayotte mo aruite'ku
Kimi to aruite'ku
Sore daku wa kawaranaide iyou ne
What lies safely hidden behind lying eyes?
Behind fake smiles,
and feigned friendship?
Finding out will be no easy task.
Enter the forest, grope in
the darkness for the unknown.
Next time on Fullmetal Alchemist: Brotherhood
Episode 24: Inside the Belly
If you move carelessly...
Nothing but pain will await
you in the inky blackness.